[
    {
        "question": "In which year did India won its first WORLD CUP?",
        "options": [
            "1983",
            "1987",
            "2011",
            "1984"
        ],
        "answer":"1983"
    },

    {
        "question":"Who among the following is known as 'GOD OF CRICKET'?",
        "options":[
            "VIRAT KOHLI",
            "MS DHONI",
            "KAPIL DEV",
            "SACHIN TENDULKAR"

        ],
        "answer":"SACHIN TENDULKAR"
    },

    {
        "question":"From which country is cricket originally originated?",
        "options":[
            "AUSTRALIA",
            "WEST-INDIES",
            "ENGLAND",
            "CANADA"


        ],
        "answer":"ENGLAND"
    },

    {
        "question":"WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY 'DIAMOND DUCK' in cricket?",
        "options":[
            "when a batter gets out 2 times continuouslly by same bowler",
            "when the batter gets out on the first legal ball faced by him",
            "when the batter gets out after 3 minutes he enters the ground",
            "when the batter gets out without facing any legal delivery"

        ],
        "answer":"when the batter gets out without facing any legal delivery"
    },

    {
        "question":"Which format of Cricket is called the ULTIMATE FORM OF CRICKET",
        "options":[
            "TEST-CRICKET",
            "T-20 CRICKET",
            "ONE-DAY INTERNATIONALS",
            "IPL"

        ],
        "answer":"TEST-CRICKET"
    },

    {
        "question":"From the following which country is currently crowned as the most times World Cup Champions?",
        "options":[
            "INDIA",
            "WEST-INDIES",
            "AUSTRALIA",
            "ENGLAND"

        ],
        "answer":"AUSTRALIA"
    },

    {
        "question":"IPL SEASON 18 played in 2025 was won by which team?",
        "options":[
            "CHENNAI SUPER KINGS",
            "MUMBAI INDIANS",
            "ROYAL CHALLENGERS BANGLORE",
            "PUNJAB KINGS"

        ],
        "answer":"ROYAL CHALLENGERS BANGLORE"
    },

    {
        "question":"Which of the following pair of teams were got banned in IPL during 2016-2017?",
        "options":[
            "RCB & CSK",
            "CSK & MI",
            "MI & RR",
            "RR & CSK"

        ],
        "answer":"RR & CSK"
    },

    {
        "question":"Among the following current fast bowlers from the world haven't played a single IPL season?",
        "options":[
            "MUSTAFIZUR RAHIM",
            "SHAHEEN SHAH AFRIDI",
            "MITCHELL STARC",
            "CHRIS WOAKES"

        ],
        "answer":"SHAHEEN SHAH AFRIDI"
    },

    {
        "question":"Which of the following batters is the leading run scorer in the IPL LEADERBOARD?",
        "options":[
            "DAVID WARNER",
            "VIRAT KOHLI",
            "ROHIT SHARMA",
            "SHIKHAR DHAWAN"

        ],
        "answer":"VIRAT KOHLI"
    }

]